# **Mohammad Alkhattab**

FrontEnd Web Developer mohammad.alkhattab77@gmail.com



05/05/1998



+963938824273

mohammad.alkhattab77@gmail.com

#### **SOCIAL MEDIA**



in http://linkedin.com/in/mohammad-alkhattab-a26024216/

**Syrian Virtual University**Master Degree in Web Science

application for management

Pure Java

Desktop application for managing a medical clinic

Al-Baath University



http://github.com/Mohammad-kh-dev



http://fb.com/MohammadAlkhattab778/

#### **PROFILE**

Holds a Bachelor's degree in Information Engineering, Al-Baath University, Department of Software Engineering, with a grade of very good. Currently, I have a master's degree in Web Science at the Syrian Virtual University, One year of experience in developing websites using modern technologies such as React js and Node Js

#### **EDUCATION**

01.2021 - present

09.2016 - 12.2021

01.2020 - 09.2020

03.2018 - 05.2018

	Faculty of Informatics Engineering, majoring in software engineering
EXPERIENCE	
06.2023 - 06.2023	Movie-Mix Web application that shows latest Movie and Popular Movie and All Details About it with Amazing And Resposive Design using React js, MUI, SCSS as a Front End and The Movie DB as Third Party api
01.2021 - 10.2021	The graduation project is a mobile application, which is an advising medical system using artificial intelligence technology The mobile app was made using flutter, The Api in Node.js and The Al Model with Python (SVM Algorithm)

Project of the year Shopik Lopik application for delivery of orders in addition to the desktop

The mobile app was made using flutter, The Api in Node.js and The Desktop App with C#



# **HOBBY**

Technology



Tennis

Communicative Creativity

**PERSONALITY** 

Punctuality Organized

# **LANGUAGES**





# **SOFTWARE SKILLS**

Word Java Flutter Node.js React JS

# **SKILLS**

- ✓ Good communication written and oral skills
- ✓ Excellent conceptual and analytical skills
- ✓ Effective interpersonal skills

